affinityclick.com 2012-06-01

# Contextual Advertising & PPC Services | Privacy

### We protect your privacy

## Effective August 1, 2009

The Privacy Policy explains the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information within and by the AffinityClick website ('AffinityClick Website') and the AffinityClick Placement Service ('Placement Service'). 'Personal Information' means individually identifiable information that would allow a party to identify you or contact you (online or in the real world). This type of information includes, for example, your name, address, telephone number, or email address (only the latter of which in certain circumstances we presently collect).

The AffinityClick Website provides marketing information and signup and account management capabilities for the Service. The information and registration capabilities on the AffinityClick Website is intended for current and prospective users of the Placement Service, including but not limited to, website owners, publishers, retailers, aggregators, distributors, carriers of media content, retail goods, listings, and more. The Placement Service is a set of web services that lets Service Partners (Bloggers) their users with Product Placement capabilities.

## AffinityClick Website and Personal Information

The AffinityClick Website requires a minimal amount of Personal Information to maintain account information and communicate with publishers who have registered with AffinityClick ('Service Partners') regarding use of the service. Additional information may be needed in the future by us or by partners in order to provide Service Partners with additional features and services. If additional information is needed, we will amend this policy and post the changes on the AffinityClick Website. We may also notify you via email of the changes although we will use good sense and reasonable judgment when doing so.

## Email Address

The AffinityClick Service uses the email address as your username. This email address is not visible to others within the system. AffinityClick will not rent, sell, or disclose your email address to third parties. AffinityClick may send Service Partners certain communications relating to their use of the Recommendations Service or changes to the Recommendations Service features, Terms of Service or the Privacy Policy.

## Cookies

AffinityClick uses cookies for Service Partners in order to save state information and to make it easier to access account informatin. This data is used only in conjunction with your use of the service and is not used separately or shared with any third party. Accessing the AffinityClick Website is not dependent on accepting cookies and all major browsers allow you to disable cookies should you desire to do so.

## Disclosure

AffinityClick may disclose account and contact names internall and with advisors, investors, and others with an interest in the use of the Recommendations Service. We limit access to specific contact information internally to only those employees and contractors who design and maintain the system information stores or who have a reasonable need to come in contact with and make use of such information for account purposes. 

## No Personal Information

AffinityClick does not collect, store, or make use of any Personal Information of anyone who uses the Recommendations Service ('Service Users'). Whereas Service Partners may collect Personal Information, AffinityClick does not come in contact with, and specifically disclaims any association with, any such information. Service Partners that use site authorization may use usernames as a key for the Recommendations Service for its users. AffinityClick has no control over the data contained within usernames and uses this information only as a database identifier.

## Cookies

We assign cookies to Service Users in order to save preference information and make it possible to use the Recommendations Service without having to register with AffinityClick or with a Service Partner. This data is used only in conjunction with your use of the Recommendations Service and is not used separately by or shared with any third party. Disabling cookies may prevent AffinityClick from providing you with personalized recommendations.

## IP Address

AffinityClick may record IP information of Service Users. Such information may be used for monitoring, and auditing use of the Recommendations Service, as well as geotargeting the content of Product Recommendations provided to end users.

## Use of Aggregated Information

We may disclose aggregated information about the use of the Recommendations Service to business partners, prospective investors, and others. Additionally, we may product industry-standard traffic reports for assessing use of the Recommendations Service. We will use information only in the aggregate in order to monitor and improve the Recommendations Service.

## General Measures

Security AffinityClick has implemented and follows industry standard measures to protect against unauthorized access to and unlawful interception or processing of Personal Information. However, no Internet site can fully eliminate security risks. AffinityClick maintains the highest level of security. All sensitive information is encrypted, and stored in a secure computer environment protected by secure firewalls to prevent unauthorized access. AffinityClick maintains multiple layers of access control and monitoring to ensure. AffinityClick does not store personally identifiable information. The cookie that we place on your computer contains a unique number but not any personal information.

## Childrens' Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA)

Children under 13 are not permitted to use the AffinityClick Website and so this privacy policy makes no provision for childrens' use of the AffinityClick Website. The Recommendations Service does not store any personal information for Service Users and any personal information collected by Service Partners is solely the responsibility of Service Partners.

## European Union Users

AffinityClick adheres to the United States/European Union Data Protection Safe Harbor Agreement, which can be located at <http://www.export.gov/safeharbor> (the 'Safe Harbor'). You expressly consent to the processing of your personal data in accordance with this privacy statement. Your personal data may be processed in the country in which it was collected and in the United States. United States laws regarding processing of personal data may be less stringent than the laws in your country.

## Outside Parties/Successors

AffinityClick will only share Personal Information with outside parties in ways that are described in this privacy statement or if we are required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary in order to conform to the edicts of the law, cooperate with law enforcement agencies, or comply with a legal process served on our website. If AffinityClick becomes part of another company, that company will possess the Peronal Information collected by AffinityClick and it will assume the rights and obligations regarding your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy. AffinityClick will notify you by email or by putting a prominent notice on the AffinityClick site before information becomes subject to a different policy.

## Personal Information Collected Under Other Circumstances

AffinityClick may collect and retain personal information from you under other circumstances, such as any communications regarding job postings, service improvements, or support issues. AffinityClick will use the same measure of care with this information as we provide to our own private information and office communications.

## Amendments

We may amend this policy at any time. Notices of amendments will be posted on our site. We may also send notices of changes via email to paying customers who have registered on the AffinityClick Website.

## Questions

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or believe that AffinityClick has not adhered to a term or terms of this Privacy Policy, please contact us by email at privacy@affinityclick.com. Written communications can be sent to AffinityClick Inc. 78 George St. Suite 201, Ottawa ON, K1N 5W1 or call us toll-free at 1 (877) 278-3625.
